health2con.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy » Health 2.0

## 1\. Introduction

Health 2.0, Inc. (“us,” “we,” or “Health 2.0″) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers, visitors, and other users of the Health 2.0 services (“Services”) provided via the Health 2.0 website (collectively, the “Website”). We created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Website or any website of Health 2.0’s partners, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Website is governed by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

## 2\. Traffic Data Collected

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Website: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Website; (4) types of web browsers used to access the Website; (5) referring source which may have sent you to the Website; and (6) other information associated with the interaction of your browser and the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”).

## 3\. Personal Information Collected

In order for you to access certain areas of the Website, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: [(1) Contact Data (such as your e-mail address and Health 2.0 password); (2) Demographic Data (such as your gender, your date of birth and your zip code. If you communicate with us by, for example, e-mail or letter, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

## 4\. Cookies

We use “cookies” to customize your experience on our Website and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website. Some of our business partners also use cookies to provide us with anonymous data and information regarding the use of our Website. We do not link the information stored in cookies directly to any of your Personal information you submit while on the Website, however. “Cookies” are small computer files that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive that contain information such as user ID, user preferences, lists of pages visited and activities conducted while browsing the Website. At your option, expense and responsibility, you may block cookies or delete cookies from your hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, you may not have access to the entire set of features of the Website.

## 5\. Storage

We store all Traffic Data and review postings indefinitely, even after “deletion,” and may archive such information elsewhere. We store all Personal Information until you request that we modify or delete it, in which case we may still wind up retaining some of that information for the reasons described in Section 15 below.

## 6\. Children

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) severely restricts what information can be collected from children under the age of 13. For this reason, children under the age of 13 in the United States are prohibited from using the Website. The Website is not directed at children, and Health 2.0 does not knowingly collect any information from individuals under the age of 13. If we learn that we have received any information from an individual under the age of 13, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or a parent or guardian) to inform him or her that he or she cannot use the Services and subsequently we will delete that information from our own servers.

## 7\. Health 2.0’s Use of Your Information

We may use your Contact Data to send you information about Health 2.0 or our products or Services, to contact you when necessary and in conjunction with your use of certain Interactive Tools. We may use your Demographic Data and/or your Traffic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website, in emails and in other communications, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences. In addition we collect information about companies and individuals who apply to speak at our conferences or complete information about themselves such as in our “startup application” forms (and other related forms) for our industry database. We also collect information directly from companies for this industry database. This information in combination with research from our own resources will be used by health 2.0 for a variety of purposes and may be shared with the public and our clients.

## 8\. Sharing of Information

We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We also share Personal Information and Traffic Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Website and/or by making certain Interactive Tools available to our users. Those business partners shall be bound to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Health 2.0 and to provide your requested services. Last, we may transfer information about you to another company in connection with a merger, sale or acquisition by or of Health 2.0. In this event, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## 9\. User Choice

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Website; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Website that require your Personal Information.

## 10\. Confidentiality and Security

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless we believe in good faith that disclosure of your Personal Information or any other information we collect about you is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order or other legal process; (2) protect the rights, property or safety of Health 2.0 or another party; (3) enforce our Terms of Use; or (4) respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third parties.

## 11\. Public Information

Any information that you may reveal in a review posting or other online discussion or forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.

## 12\. Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Although we make good faith efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, you should understand that there is no such thing as complete security, and we do not guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law.

## 13\. Lost or Stolen Information

You must promptly notify us if your Contact Data is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that Contact Data from your account and update our records accordingly.

## 14\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy so please review it frequently. If we do, then we will notify you here, as well as by posting a notice on our Website, along with a description of any changes (material or otherwise) and, where appropriate, a link to the modified policy so that you can review it. In all cases, use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

## 15\. Controlling Your Personal Information

As a registered user of the Website, you can modify some of the Personal Information you have included in your profile by logging in and accessing your account. You cannot, however, change your username once you have registered. Upon your request, Health 2.0 will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete your account and the Personal Information in your profile; however, it may be impossible to remove your account without some residual information being retained by Health 2.0. Registered users who wish to close their account should contact “privacy@health2con.com”.

## 16\. Links to Other Websites

The Website contains links to third party websites to which Health 2.0 has no affiliation. Health 2.0 does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. Some websites may have the look and feel of our Website. Please be aware that you may be on a different site and that this Privacy Policy only covers our Website. Should you decide to visit one of these third party websites, we suggest that you read its privacy policy.

## 17\. Contacts

If you have any comments, concerns or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at “privacy@health2con.com”.

or

Health 2.0, LLC.

350 Townsend, #403, San Francisco, CA 94107

Phone: (415) 992 – 7527

Last Updated on January 08, 2013.

Copyright 2013, Health 2.0, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

Note: On January 7, 2013 we changed section 7 & 8 to reflect that this site is now collecting company information for our database and renumbered sections 4 onwards to correct a numbering error”
